Guide to the Everett Cherrington Hughes Papers 1922-1982
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Boston College, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Donald J. White, dean, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Boston College, honorary degree, June 5, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Boston College, J. Donald Monan, president, 1972-1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Boston College, recruitment of faculty, 1968, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Boston College, special fund, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Boston University, African Studies Center, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Bourg, Carroll, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Bourgeois, Charles S., 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Bramson, Leon, 1959-1969 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Brandeis University, general, 1962-1979 (Box 12, Folder 19-20)
  - Brandeis University, bank robbery-murder affair, September 1970 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Brandeis University, Berkowitz case, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Brandeis University, bursar's office, 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Brandeis University, Department of Sociology, general, 1961-1971 (Box 13, Folder 4-8)
  - Brandeis University, Department of Sociology, 1972-1979 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
  - Brandeis University, Department of Sociology, faculty meetings, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Brandeis University, Department of Sociology, faculty meetings, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Brandeis University, Department of Sociology, faculty meetings, 1971-1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Brandeis University, Department of Sociology, faculty recruitment, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Brandeis University, Department of Sociology, policy, 1965-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Brandeis University, Department of Sociology, Maurice Stein, chairman, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Brandeis University, Gazette, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Brandeis University, Gough-Aberle case, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
  - Brandeis University, graduate exams, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Brandeis University, graduate and undergraduate students, 1962-1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Brandeis University, Heller School, study of violence, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Brandeis University, Lillian Levi, secretary, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Brandeis University, Lillian Levi, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Brandeis University, Lillian Levi, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Brandeis University, Lillian Levi, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Brandeis University, library reserve lists, 1963-1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Brandeis University, list of courses taught, 1968-1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Brandeis University, medical sociology training grant, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Brandeis University, presidential possibilities, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Brandeis University, program in basic medical science, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Brandeis University, project in social organization of medical care, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Brandeis University, public affairs, 1963-1967 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Brandeis University, Charles I. Schottland, Dean of Faculty, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Brandeis University, student and faculty lists, 1970-1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Brandeis University, student sit-in, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Brandeis University, study of violence, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Brandeis University, vitae for job applicants, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Brandt, Barbara, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Braude, Lee, 1960-1976 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Brazeau, Jacques, 1960-1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Brazeau, Jacques, 1960-1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Briggs, Channing, 1958-1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Brim, Orville G., Jr., 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Broom, Leonard, 1965-1975 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Brown Reprints, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Bruyn, Severyn, 1964-1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Bryant, Clifton D., 1969-1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Bucher, Rue, 1958-1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Bulmer, Martin, 1971-1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Bunzel, J.H., "Life and Death of the Verein f¸r Sozialpolitik," 1968 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Burgess, Ernest Watson, memorial service, 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Burnet, Jean R., 1963-1976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Burns, Lawton Robert, 1970-1977 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Burns, Tom, 1964-1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - C, general, 1956-1982 (Box 17, Folder 1-5)
  - Cahnman, Werner, 1960-1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Cambridge Forum, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Campanis, Paul, 1965-1977 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Canada, Royal Commission on the Status of Women, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Canadian Broadcasting Company, "French Canada in Transition," radio transcripts, 1951-1952 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Canadian Peace Research Institute, 1963-1965 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Canadian Political Science Association and Canadian Journal of Economics and Political Science, 1959-1965 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Canadian Research Center for Anthropology, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Canadian Sociology and Anthropology Association, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
  - Canadian Sociology and Anthropology Association, meeting, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Canadian Sociology and Anthropology Association, meeting, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
  - Canadian Sociology and Anthropology Association, meeting, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 8-9)
  - Canadian Sociology and Anthropology Association, meeting, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Canadian Sociology and Anthropology Association, meeting, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Caplow, Theodore, 1962-1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Carden, Maren Lockwood, 1969-1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Carlin, Jerome, 1957-1966 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, project on the student condition, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Carsch, Henry, 1965-1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Carter, Barbara, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Cassidy, Sally, 1958-1977 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Cavan, Ruth Shonle, 1967-1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Cayton, Horace R., 1963-1969 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Cedar Crest College, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Center for Research in Careers, Harvard University, 1963-1967 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Chall, Leo P., 1967-1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Chicago Public Schools, 1949-1961 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Chicago School Irregulars, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Chow, Yung-Teh, 1969-1975 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Ciacci, Margherita, 1973-1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Clark, S. Delbert, 1938-1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Clark University, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Cobb, Robert P., concerning Scholars' Conference on African Literature, 1965. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - College Research Center, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Collins, Orvis, 1963-1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Colvard, Richard Maltby, 1958-1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Committee for the Restoration of Democratic Government in Greece, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Community Relations Commission, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Community Studies Incorporated, 1961-1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Cornerhouse Fund, 1969-1980 (Box 20, Folder 11-14)
  - Coser, Lewis A., 1965, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Cox, David M., 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Cultural island committee, 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Current Anthropology, 1959, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - D, general, 1961-1973 (Box 21, Folder 3-5)
  - Daedalus, article on the professions, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Daedalus, general, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Daneau, Marcel, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Dargue, Ralph H., 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Dartmouth College, 1964-1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Allison, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Davis, Edward, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)
  - Davis, Fred, 1969-1973 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Dawson, Carl A., 1927-1955 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - DeBaggis, Agostino M., 1963-1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Deutsche Gesellschaft f¸r Soziologie, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Deutscher, Irwin, 1962-1971 (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
  - Dexter, Lewis A., 1961-1972 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Dibner, Susan Schmidt, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Donovan, John D., 1970 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Dorsey Press, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Doyle, Bertram W., 1968-1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Duke University, program in Quebec studies, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Drake, St. Clair, and Cayton, Horace R., Black Metropolis, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - E, general, 1959-1980 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Eastern Sociological Society, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 14-16)
  - Eastern Sociological Society, 1971-1979 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Sociological Society, meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
  - Eastern Sociological Society, meeting, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Sociological Society, meeting, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - ...diteur officiel du QuÈbec, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Education papers, 1959-1965 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Eggan, Dorothy, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Eisenstadt, S. N., 1952 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Elkin, Frederick, 1959-1969 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Elling, Ray H., 1963-1966 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Emerson, Robert, 1963-1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Epstein, Martin, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Ericksen, E. Gordon, 1969-1976 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Etzkorn, Peter, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Evans, Thomas C., 1969-1976 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Eweson, Dorothy, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - F, general, 1941-1979 (Box 24, Folder 2-5)
  - Faith, Don R., 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Falardeau, Jean-Charles, 1940-1980 (Box 24, Folder 7-9)
  - Faris, Robert E. L., 1961-1970 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Faulkner, Robert R., 1973 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Federal Statistics Users' Conference, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Fei Hsiao-Tung, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Ferguson, Charles A., 1966-1972 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Fichter, Joseph H., 1950-1954 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Finestone, Harold, 1959-1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Fish, Virginia, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Fishman, Joshua A., 1965-1975 (Box 25, Folder 6-8)
  - Fisk University, 1954-1957 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Floro, George K., 1974-1979 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Fontaine, Yves, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Foote, Nelson N., 1966-1977 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Ford Foundation, 1962-1967 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Fortes, Meyer, 1959-1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Foss, Daniel, 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Foundationman study, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
  - Fox, RenÈe C., 1960-1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Free Press, 1947-1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Freedman, Jonathan, A., 1963-1968 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Freeman, Howard, 1965-1968 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Freidson, Eliot, 1951-1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - French, D. G., 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Freymann, John Gordon, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Friedmann, Georges, 1947-1960, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Fulbright-Hays Program with the United Kingdom, 1963-1968 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Fukutake, Tadashi, 1962-1975 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Funk and Wagnalls, Incorporated, 1958-1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Future Resources and Development, Incorporated (FRD), 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - G, general, 1958-1979 (Box 27, Folder 2-4)
  - Gagnon, John, 1958-1965 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Gans, Herbert, 1963-1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Garigue, Philippe, 1956-1964 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Geer, Blanche, 1960-1982 (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
  - Geertz, Clifford, 1974-1980 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Gertler, Maynard, 1965-1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Ghurye, G.S., 1958-1978 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Gilfillan, S. Colum, 1970-1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Glazer, Nathan, 1959-1979 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Glick, Clarence E., 1964-1966 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Gobetz, Giles Edward, 1969-1977 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Goffman, Erving, 1955-1978 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
  - Gold, Raymond L., 1958-1966 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Goldschmidt, Walter, 1974-1980 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Gordimer, Nadine, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Gouldner, Alvin W., 1958-1977 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Grady, John, 1970-1977 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Greeley, Andrew M., 1960-1979 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Griessman, B. Eugene, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Griff, Mason, 1958-1973 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Grimshaw, Allen D., 1967-1975 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Gross, Edward, 1958-1974 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Group Health Insurance, Incorporated, symposium on the future of the personal physician, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Groves, Murray, 1965-1970 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Guillemin, Jeanne, 1971-1979 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - Guindon, Hubert, 1959-1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Gum, William L., 1964-1976 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Gumperz, John J., 1970 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Gusfield, Joseph R., 1959 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Gusfield, Joseph R., 1959-1970 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - H, general, 1958-1980 (Box 29, Folder 8-12)
  - Habenstein, Robert W., 1969-1977 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Habenstein, Robert W., interview with Everett C. Hughes, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Haerle, Rudolf K., Jr., 1962-1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Hagstrom, Warren O., 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Hale, William H., 1952-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Hall, Edward T., 1961-1978 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Hall, Oswald, 1938-1978 (Box 30, Folder 5-8)
  - Halpern, Joel M., 1963-1970 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Hansen, Millard, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Hare, Nathan, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Harper, Douglas, 1975-1980 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Harper and Row, Publishers, 1962-1965 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Harris, Natalie Allon, 1968-1978 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Harris, Natalie Allon, 1968-1978 (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - Hartner, Willy, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Hartwell, Elizabeth A., 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Harvard Educational Review, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Encyclopedia of American Ethnic Groups, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Harvard University, ad hoc committee on Canadian chair, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Harvard University, Department of Sociology, 1971-1978 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Harvard University, Frazier Lectures, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Harvard University, Overseers to visit the Department of Sociology, 1970-1972 (Box 31, Folder 10-11)
  - Harvard University, Overseers to visit the Department of Sociology, 1972-1977 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Harvard University, School of Public Health, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Harvard University Press, 1963-1973 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Harvest House Limited Publishers, 1965-1968 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Havighurst, Robert, 1967-1973 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Hawkins, Charles, 1958-1962 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Hawley, Amos, 1968-1979 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Health Information Foundation, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Heberle, Rudolf, 1958-1982 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Helle, Horst J., 1967 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Hill, Mozell C., 1946-1963 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Holley, Thomas B., 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Hollowell, Peter G., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Holmstrom, Lynda L., 1966-1970 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Hopper, Rex D., concerning Project Camelot, 1962-1967 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Horowitz, Irving Louis, 1966-1976 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Horowitz, Irving Louis, Transaction/Society, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Horton, Donald, 1952-1959 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1963, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Howell, Nancy, 1965-1973 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Hughes family correspondence (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Human Organization, Journal of the Society of Applied Anthropology, 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - I, general, 1938-1979 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Ianni, Francis A. J., 1962 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), 1968 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Ichheiser, Gustav, 1943-1976 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Imada, Yoko, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Institute for Advanced Studies, Vienna, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Advanced Study, Princeton, 1967-1971 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Institute of Race Relations, 1961-1969 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Intern study, Harvard School of Medicine, 1952-1957 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - International Congress of Psychology, Moscow, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1962-1967 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - International Journal of the Sociology of Language, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - International Sociological Association, 1958-1974 (Box 33, Folder 2-3)
  - International Sociological Association, meeting, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - International Sociological Association, meeting, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 5-6)
  - Israel, reprints, 1951-1968 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Iutcovich, Mark, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - J, general, 1958-1979 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Jackson, John D., 1965 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Jacobs, Ruth Harriet, 1966-1977 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Janowitz, Morris, 1964-1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Japanese Americans in wartime, articles, 1941-1944 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Japanese sociologists, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Joffe, Carole, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - John Wiley and Sons, Incorporated, Publishers, 1964-1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Earl, 1964-1978 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Jones, Lewis M., 1958-1970 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Jones, Roberto Cuba, 1959-1979 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Jossey-Bass Incorporated, Publishers, 1969-1976 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Junker, Buford H., 1955-1978 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - K, general, 1954-1979 (Box 34, Folder 12-14)
  - Kahl, Joseph A., 1964 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Karp, David, 1973-1979 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1966-1969 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Keyfitz, Nathan, 1959-1973 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Khleif, Bud B., 1963-1979 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Killian, Lewis, 1965-1975 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Kilson, Martin L., 1969-1975 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Kimball, Solon, 1959-1981 (Box 35, Folder 7-8)
  - Kimura, Yukiko, 1952-1965 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Kincheloe, Samuel C., 1962-1978 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Kinnane, Mary, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Kleining, Gerhard, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Knowles, Asa S., 1967 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Knowlton, Clark S., 1973 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Kolb, William, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Korea, 1958-1962 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Kracauer, Siegfried, 1959-1964 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Krause, Elliott A., 1969-1976 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Kriesberg, Louis, 1962-1973 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Krol, John, Cardinal, American priest study, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
  - Kwan, Kian, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - L, general, 1957-1982 (Box 36, Folder 6-9)
  - Lambiri-Dimaki, Jane, 1958-1976 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Lamontagne, Jacques, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Lamy, Paul, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Landes, Ruth, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Language problems in advanced urban and industrial regions, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Laufer, Robert, 1965-1969 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - LaViolette, Forrest, 1951-1969 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Lawton, William C., 1950-1964 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Lazarsfeld, Paul, 1958-1969 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Learned Societies conferences, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Lee, Alfred McClung, 1963-1974 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Lee, Shu-Ching, 1962-1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Lentz, Edith, 1952-1960 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Leventman, Seymour, 1971-1977 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Levine, Donald, including papers on Georg Simmel, 1961-1971 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Levy, Charles, 1959-1975 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Levy, Charles, 1959-1975 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, Ralph, 1962-1966 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Librairie Beauchemin LimitÈe, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Lieberson, Stanley, 1961-1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Light, Donald, 1964-1975 (Box 38, Folder 5-7)
  - Lind, Andrew W., 1959-1975 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Loeb, Charlotte I., 1972 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - London, Howard, 1972-1978 (Box 38, Folder 10-11)
  - London, Howard, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Loomis, Charles P., 1957-1965 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Lopata, Helena Znaniecki, 1966-1980 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Lorwin, Val R., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Luckmann, Thomas, 1969-1972 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Lyman, Elizabeth, 1958-1976 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Lyman, Stanford M., 1974-1978 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - M, general, 1935-1982 (Box 39, Folder 4-9)
  - MacCannell, Dean, 1972-1975 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Macdonell, Allan, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Magill, Dennis William, 1976-1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Mahmood, Syed Hamid, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Maintenant, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Marcson, Simon, 1964-1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Marquis Who's Who, Incorporated, 1970-1976 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Marsh, Leonard, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Marshall, Thomas H., 1959-1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Marx, Gary, 1970-1977 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Maslow, Abraham H., 1953-1970 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Symposium on Professional Education, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 10-11)
  - Massachusetts Sociological Association, 1966-1971 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - MassÈ, Jacqueline C., 1959-1978 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Matthews, Fred H., 1964-1980 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Maxwell, Sherrolyn, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Maynard, Albert D., 1960 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - McCall, Bevode C., 1964-1975 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - McCall, George J., 1962 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - McDowell, Sophia, 1959-1968 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - McGill University, 1955-1965, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - McGill University, Adair Lectures, 1964-1965 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1961-1979 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - McMillan, Robert, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Mead, Margaret, 1959-1979 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Meier, August, 1971-1978 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Merrill, Francis E., 1964-1965 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Merton, Robert K., 1957-1973 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Mifflen, Francis J., 1971-1974 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Miller, S. M., 1965-1974 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Mintz, Norbett L., 1962 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Mirsky, Norman, 1969-1972 (Box 41, Folder 14-15)
  - Miyakawa, T. Scott, 1961-1973 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Mogey, John, 1962-1970 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Moment, David, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Monane, Joseph, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Monast, Serge, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Monteith College Library Program, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Moore, Joan W., 1961-1972 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Morris, Robert, 1967-1971 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Mulherin, James P., 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Murra, John, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Murray, Stephen, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Myers, Jerome K., 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - N, general, 1958-1980 (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
  - Nathanson, Constance, 1959-1973 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - National Academy of Education, 1972-1976, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1961-1963, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Sciences, M.H. Trytten, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - National Commission on United Methodist Higher Education, 1973-1975 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - National Opinion Research Center, Louis Kriesberg and Vickie Beale, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - National Opinion Research Center, Peter H. Rossi, 1960, James A. Davis and Peter H. Rossi, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - National Opinion Research Center, manuscripts, 1960, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - National Opinion Research Center, research proposal, "General Practice in the United States," n.d. (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - National Science Foundation, 1962-1967 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - National Society of Professional Engineers, 1974-1977 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - National Student Association, Conference on the Educational Ideal and the Academic Structure, working papers, March 2-3, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 2)